<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="es">
  <generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.8.1">Jekyll</generator>
  
  
  <link href="https://yanez.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <updated>2018-05-03T23:27:57+02:00</updated>
  <id>https://yanez.io//</id>

  
    <title type="html">yanez.io</title>
  

  
    <subtitle>Reflexiones, experiencias e introspección personal de una persona con una vida ligada a la tecnología, al estrés y al deseo de construir cosas nuevas y diferentes.</subtitle>
  

  
    <author>
        <name>Francis Yáñez</name>
      
        <email>hi@yanez.io</email>
      
      
    </author>
  

  
  
    <entry xml:lang="en">
      
      <title type="html">Dear English readers</title>
      

      

      <link rel="canonical" href="https://yanez.io/en/2018-05-01/dear-english-readers" type="text/html" hreflang="en" title="Dear English readers" />

      
      
        <link rel="alternate"  href="https://yanez.io/en/2018-05-01/dear-english-readers" type="text/html" hreflang="en" title="Dear English readers" />
      

      <published>2018-05-01T00:00:00+02:00</published>
      <updated>2018-05-01T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
      <id>https://yanez.io/en/2018-05-01/dear-english-readers</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://yanez.io/en/2018-05-01/dear-english-readers">&lt;p&gt;I apologize as I’m not a native English speaker and the majority of the publications in this personal blog will be in Spanish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When using a technical language, I feel entirely comfortable in English, and there so I’ll write those technical articles first in English and then translate them into Spanish, so this blog has both versions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I’ll be writing a lot of nontechnical articles too like different kind of reviews about books, movies and music, personal stuff and news articles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t feel comfortable enough yet to use English as my primary language for those nontechnical articles, so I’ll write them in Spanish and won’t probably have an English version.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is why this site will have more Spanish content than English, and I apologize in advance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for your comprehension!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to know more about me in English, please visit this &lt;a href=&quot;/about-me&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      
        <author>
            <name>Francis Yáñez</name>
          
            <email>hi@yanez.io</email>
          
          
        </author>
      

      

      
        <summary type="html">I apologize as I’m not a native English speaker and the majority of the publications in this personal blog will be in Spanish.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
  
</feed>
